


Divisible by :
- 2 : the number is even (unit digit is 0, 2, 4, 6 or 8)
- 3 : the sum of all digits is divisible by 3
- 4 : the last 2 digits (ten and unit) is divisible by 4
- 5 : the unit digit is 0 or 5
- 6 : the number is even (divisible by 2) and divisible by 3
- 8 : the last 3 digits (hundred, ten, unit) is divisible by 8
- 9 : the sum of all digits is divisible by 9
- 10 : Unit digit is 0

